Lexsa Campbell

Front-end Software Engineer

Recent bootcamp graduate with a passion for visual design and a performance marketing background spanning SAAS, ecommerce, and telecom brands. Skilled at collaborating across marketing, product, design, and engineering teams in order to build exceptional customer experiences and drive revenue growth.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Springboard, Remote Software Engineering Fellow

04/2022 - 02/2023

- 700+ hours of hands-on course material, with 1:1 industry experience mentor oversight, and completion of four in-depth portfolio projects
- Mastered skills in front-end web development, back-end web development, databases, and data structures and algorithms

Leaf Group, Los Angeles, California

Worked directly for Society6 and Saatchi Art D2C ecommerce brands

Director, Acquisition Marketing

08/2021 - 03/2022

- Owned eight-figure annual paid marketing budget, strategy, and revenue targets spanning digital channels; scaled spend and revenue +180% within two years while exceeding return-on-ad-spend (ROAS) targets
- Drove cross-functional improvements in data analytics, customer attribution modeling, and channel testing methodology
- Reported directly into senior leadership team, managed three direct reports and multiple agency/partner relationships

Senior Manager, Acquisition Marketing

10/2019 - 07/2021

• Achieved 60% year-over-year paid revenue growth through incrementality testing, multi-touch attribution adoption, and new channel growth

Manager, Acquisition Marketing

01/2019 - 10/2019

 Managed acquisition marketing efforts across Google and Facebook properties; delivered +23% revenue growth year-over-year

Dropbox, San Francisco, California Performance Marketing Manager

09-2017 - 12/2018

- Led strategy, optimization, and day-to-day management of paid search programs; achieved 30% growth in Dropbox Business sign-ups and a 55% reduction in cost-per-acquisition through rigorous A/B testing and analysis
- Launched Dropbox's first paid media program into APAC markets and surpassed revenue launch target by 42%

Red Ventures, Fort Mill, South Carolina

Full-funnel customer acquisition firm, worked on Verizon and AT&T accounts

Paid Search Associate 05/2014 – 06/2015

• Partnered directly with the UX team to develop and execute a quarterly hypothesis-driven testing roadmap; efforts drove a 35% year-over-year lift in on-site conversion rate

CONTACT

- · 502 777 6952
- · lexsacampbell.com
- lexsacampbell@gmail.com
- · github.com/lexsac

SKILLS

Programming Languages:

- JavaScript (ES6)
- · HTML
- · CSS

Libraries and Frameworks:

- · React.js
- Material UI
- · Styled Components

Tools and Platforms:

- Git
- Figma
- Google Tag Manager
- Google Analytics

PROJECTS

Single-Page Portfolio

Responsive single-page portfolio site

Built with: HTML, CSS, Figma

 https://github.com/lexsac/ single-page-portfolio

Space Tourism Site

Multi-page React app Built with: React, CSS, Figma

 https://github.com/lexsac/ space-tourism-react

EDUCATION

Yale School of Management

Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.)

New Haven, Connecticut

- GMAT: 960 (99th percentile)
- Forté scholarship recipient
- Summer Fellow, Yale Entrepreneurial Institute

Vanderbilt University

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) Major: Economics Nashville, Tennessee

• GPA: 3.8/4.0, Dean's List